{
  "1": {
    "name": "Know Your Lockdown",
    "isRevealed:": false,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "In what month did the first national lockdown begin in England?",
        "answer": "March",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the lowest 'COVID alert level' under the English regional lockdown system?",
        "answer": "Medium",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "How many tiers does the Scottish regional lockdown system have?",
        "answer": "5",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "What does SAGE stand for?",
        "answer": "Scientific Advisory Group for Emergencies",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the Government Chief Scientific Adviser: Chris Whitty or Patrick Vallance?",
        "answer": "Patrick Vallance",
        "isRevealed": false
      }
    ],
    "currentQuestionIndex": 0
  },
  "2": {
    "name": "Landmarks",
    "isRevealed:": false,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "What landmark is this?",
        "answer": "Great Wall of China",
        "isRevealed": false,
        "hasImage": true
      },
      {
        "question": "What landmark is this?",
        "answer": "The Colosseum",
        "isRevealed": false,
        "hasImage": true
      },
      {
        "question": "What landmark is this?",
        "answer": "Co-op Bank / Stockport Pyramid",
        "isRevealed": false,
        "hasImage": true
      },
      {
        "question": "What landmark is this?",
        "answer": "Niagara Falls",
        "isRevealed": false,
        "hasImage": true
      },
      {
        "question": "What landmark is this?",
        "answer": "The Trafford Centre",
        "isRevealed": false,
        "hasImage": true
      }
    ],
    "currentQuestionIndex": 0
  },
  "3": {
    "name": "Film",
    "isRevealed:": false,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Which Disney cartoon featuring Eddie Murphy had a live action remake released this year?",
        "answer": "Mulan",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Which film won the Oscar for Best Picture this year?",
        "answer": "Parasite",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the James Bond film whose release was postponed due to COVID-19?",
        "answer": "No Time To Die",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the second Indiana Jones film?",
        "answer": "Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Which actor plays Rick O'Connell in The Mummy and George in George of the Jungle?",
        "answer": "Brendan Frasier",
        "isRevealed": false
      }
    ],
    "currentQuestionIndex": 0
  },
  "4": {
    "name": "Music",
    "isRevealed:": false,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "What is the most viewed YouTube video of all time?",
        "answer": "Baby Shark",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "According to the lyrics of Summer Nights from the musical Grease, what did Sandy and Danny drink together?",
        "answer": "Lemonade",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the smallest string instrument in an orchestra?",
        "answer": "Violin",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "How many semitones are there in a perfect fifth?",
        "answer": "7",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Which symptom of COVID-19 is also the name of a song by Dame Shirley Bassey?",
        "answer": "Fever",
        "isRevealed": false
      }
    ],
    "currentQuestionIndex": 0
  },
  "5": {
    "name": "TV",
    "isRevealed:": false,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "üå∂ üê∑",
        "answer": "Peppa Pig",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "üë©üèΩ‚Äç‚öïÔ∏è ü§∑üèæ‚Äç‚ôÇÔ∏è",
        "answer": "Doctor Who",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "‚ô•Ô∏è üèù",
        "answer": "Love Island",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "üßõ‚Äç‚ôÇÔ∏è ‚¨áÔ∏è",
        "answer": "Countdown",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "üóû üåÉ",
        "answer": "News Night",
        "isRevealed": false
      }
    ],
    "currentQuestionIndex": 0
  },
  "6": {
    "name": "Sport",
    "isRevealed:": false,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Which Premier League team has the southernmost stadium?",
        "answer": "Brighton & Hove Albion",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "True or false: golf courses in England have to shut during the November national lockdown",
        "answer": "True",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "How many bails are there in a game of cricket?",
        "answer": "Four",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "True or false: squash balls are solid rubber",
        "answer": "False",
        "isRevealed": false
      },
      {
        "question": "How many players are on a squash team?",
        "answer": "Four",
        "isRevealed": false
      }
    ],
    "currentQuestionIndex": 0
  }
}
